Unbelievable.
No more mutants.
No more giant moths.
- Such a better world.
- For you. maybe.
I lost my hawem.
Mm. you know those weren't
healthy relationships.
It was all consensual.
Sex for food.
I looked everywhere. No Denise.
Eh. she must have been
too far away
from the interdimensional bubble
cweated by
the Weonard/Sheldon device.
What the hell does that mean?
Well. I don't know.
I'm just wiffing.
- Hey. Stuart.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I can't believe I lost the love
of my life and I get you.
Let's not forget. he killed Raj.
Well. now.
there are two possibilities.
One. the world we were just in
no wonger exists.
in which case
I did not "kill Waj."
Two. that world
and this world are part of
an infinite number of worlds.
in which case I killed one
of an infinite number of Wajs.
Mathematicawy.
a wounding error.
Oh. excuse me.
I was gonna buy that book.
Oh! Oh. I'm sorry.
Here. I had no idea.
It was unintentional.
- I forgive you.
- I appreciate that.
And I appreciate you.
Uh. how much do you want
for Superman and Lex Luthor:
Best Buddies Number 30?
Best Buddies?
Let me see that.
What the hell?
Stuart. look at this.
This whole wall
is Archie comics.
What? I don't carry Archie.
You do now.
Wichie Wich: Effective Altruist
Number 12.
Richie Rich what?
Something's wrong here.
You must have screwed up
the machine. Stuart.
I screwed up?
You killed the one guy that knew
how to use the damn thing.
Uh. fellas. we're all friends.
- Yeah. no arguing.
- Stay out of it.
You're the one who pushed
the stupid button.
What was I supposed to do?
You're the one who--
We should go.
- That's a lovely idea.
- Thank you.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Uh-oh. that's not supposed
to be there.
- What just happened?
- I don't know.
I have a hypothesis.
I'm listening.
Did you notice the thing
on the back of your necks?
What? What thing?
Humor me.
- Oh. boy.
- Not good.
Now. try having an argument.
What are you talking about?
That's gotta be the stupidest--.
You might be onto something.
♪ Stuart tries
To reset our lives ♪
♪ But he fails
To save the universe ♪
♪ He's our only chance
And he tries and he tries ♪
♪ But he fails
To save the universe ♪
♪ Stuart tries ♪
- ♪ He tries ♪
- ♪ But he fails ♪
♪ Fails ♪
- ♪ Fails ♪
♪ Stuart fails! ♪
Gentlemen. we are in hell.
Really? Everyone's being
so nice to each other.
Hi!
Yeah. they have devices
implanted in their necks
to make them nice.
Would you rather push the button
on the Sheldon/Leonard thingy
and try another universe?
No. thanks. We could wind up
somewhere worse.
Like where humans
are a meat source
for a highly evolved
wizard people?
Yeah. like that.
Or one where everyone's French.
but no one speaks French.
What's that?
Best guess?
A giant floating obelisk with
no apparent means of propulsion?
You are weawy getting
on my nerve.
Stop talking.
Another piece of the puzzle?
Maybe.
I think what we're looking at
is your classic
totalitarian dystopia
with a dollop
of mind control surveillance.
- A dollop?
- It means a small serving.
Yeah. I know what it means--
I know what it means!
So. here's what I'm thinking.
We need to go to Caltech
and find Weonard and Sheldon.
Okay. you do that.
I'll try to find Denise.
With all due respect...
...perhaps we should
stick together.
And you are entitled
to your opinion.
but I am in love
with this woman.
and I have to find her.
I understand.
- Thank you.
- Hmm.
Idiot.
Shit!
- Hi. Can you help us?
- Well. I certainly hope so.
Great. We are wooking
for Dr. Weonard Hofstadter
or perhaps Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Do you have an appointment?
- Uh...
- No.
Oh. I wish you had
an appointment.
- Can we make one?
- Of course.
Then we'd like
to make an appointment.
I don't make appointments.
You'd have to contact
their personal assistants.
Okay. Mm!
And h... how do we
get in touch with them?
You call them.
Can you tell us their numbers?
Sure can't.
We are in the middle of a cwisis
and we weawy need
to talk to them.
Sir. I would ask you
not to raise your voice.
I'm not waising my voice.
I'm just trying to say--
Sorry.
We're new to this whole
button-in-the neck thing.
Ow!
Oh... Oh. thank God.
Yes?
- Denise?
- Who is it?
- It's Stuart.
Oh!
What a pleasant surprise.
Come on in.
Gary. you'll never guess
who's here.
- You need to be cool.
- Got it. Can we start over?
By all means.
Here's the thing.
Weonard Hofstadter
and Sheldon Cooper
built a vewy special device.
Well. if anyone here
could build a special device.
it's certainly those two.
It certainly is.
You're doing good.
Anyway. the device has torn
the fabwic of weality.
possibly causing
the universe to cowapse
- and then weegwo.
- Weegwo?
- Yeah. weegwo.
- What is weegwo?
Weegwo.
Uh. uh. like a plant weegwos.
- Weegwo?
- Wee-gwo.
- Weegwo.
You stupid. stupid--
He has trouble
with the letter "R."
Oh! "Regrow."
That makes more sense.
Okay. I'm just gonna say it.
and forgive me
if it doesn't make sense.
Denise. you and I
are destined to be together.
and I have come
from a parallel universe...
uh. to claim you.
Well. that is really something.
Mind-blowing.
Okay. you're...
So. you're like a running joke
- in all this. aren't you?
- Sorry?
Uh. it's not important.
All I can tell you
is that you don't have to live
with this AI thing
controlling you.
- How?
- It's a little complicated.
I've got this machine
back at the store that... it...
I-- I-- I-- I-- It... It--
You're just gonna
have to trust me.
- May I ask a question?
- Of course.
I realize how upsetting
this must be for you.
I'm not upset.
Denise. are you upset?
- No. of course not.
- What do you want her to do?
Well...
Like I said.
I want her to leave you
and... and come with me.
Wow. Denise?
To be honest. it's tempting.
Really?
- Sure.
- Sure?
But... that...
So. you're cool with this?
- Yeah. she can't stand me.
- I can't.
- Uh. so why stay together?
- Hmm.
Well. if I leave.
then Gary would be upset.
Traumatized.
And we've learned
not to upset each other.
- 'Cause it hurts.
- Ouch.
So. wait. you know
that she's unhappy
and you're fine with it?
She's only unhappy
when she's sober.
and that's not very often.
No. no. I have a little problem
with the...
...so...
Mm-hmm.
Okay. What kind of crazy
upside-down world is this?
Denise. you have the right
to be happy!
There's no reason
to stay with somebody
that makes you mis--
Yeah.
- Rum and Coke?
- Diet Coke. please.
Coming up.
- Let me...
- Yes.
- Hello.
You know. in another universe.
I worked in this building.
Really? In what department?
Geology.
Oh. that's not
in this building anymore.
W... Why not?
They needed to make room
for the important sciences.
Uh. geology is
an important science.
And yet they moved it
into the storage room
behind the gym.
W... W... Why would you take
a field of study that examines
the physical structure
of the planet...
Nice twy. Dumbo.
I did not care for that woman.
Also. I wet myself.
Lucky you're wearing dark pants.
Oh. yeah.
This can't be good.
Hey. fellas. Got a minute?
What's going on?
I'm Officer McCaffrey.
This is Officer Denison.
Call me "Steve."
And we're going to be
your arresting officers today.
What did we do?
"What did we do?"
- I love these guys.
- Oh. yeah.
Seriously. what did we do?
Well. when people
keep getting upset.
- it becomes a police matter.
- Don't you worry.
Everything's going
to be explained
at the re-education center.
I don't like
the sound of that.
Well. I hope you like the sound
of complimentary
bottles of water.
- Hmm.
- And granola bars.
'cause they're waiting for you
in the back of the car.
Wook. a fwoating obewisk.
Oh. dear.
- I'll just get in the car.
- Yeah.
- Oh. thank you.
Right this way.
Sparkling or flat?
Hello! I'm theater. film.
and television's
Christine Baranski.
I bet you're wondering
what you're doing here.
Simple answer.
you have been non-compliant.
"Ouch!" Am I right?
Well. maybe this is
a good opportunity
to remind ourselves.
and by ourselves. I mean you.
why this is the best
of all possible worlds.
I loved the first Mamma Mia!
The second one
was kind of milking it.
Not too long ago.
human beings were
on the verge of extinction.
Violence. crime. and war
were running rampant.
That's when our government
turned to the whiz kids
in Silicon Valley and said...
"Can you save us
from ourselves?"
And boy. oh. boy. did they!
Well. not so much them.
but the AI they built.
Shortly after it turned
on its creators.
brutally killing them all...
...the AI implanted
electronic punishment devices
in everyone's brain stem.
Mix that with
a little aerial surveillance.
and before you know it.
a world free of anger.
war. and insult comics.
Does it work all the time?
If it did. you wouldn't be here
beginning your 30-month
re-education process.
Will that hurt?
Like a motherfucker.
But when you walk out of here.
you will be one happy amigo.
- We gotta escape.
- How?
I don't know.
but I'll figure it out.
- I'm glad we didn't escape.
- Oh. me too.
It was an honor
being wehabilitated
with you fewas.
I've got a sweet tooth.
Who's up for some fro-yo?
Oh. love it. My treat!
- Aw.
- Thanks. buddy.
- Huh? What's happening?
- I think we're being abducted.
Well. so much for yogurt.
- Stuart?
- Yeah?
You okay?
I am. yeah.
Thank you for asking.
I'm okay. too.
Zack?
- You know me?
- Of course.
I... I mean.
not from this universe.
Uh. I mean.
it... it... it... it...
N... Never mind.
Well. regardless.
consider yourself rescued.
Rescued? They let us out.
After wocking us up
for two and a half years?
- Really?
- Yes. Weawy.
Wow. That's embarrassing.
- Who are you guys?
- Oh. sorry.
Uh. yes. we are the Resistance.
and this is our headquarters.
Used to be
an Amazon shipping center.
We took over the lease.
- Oh. yeah.
- It was a long process.
It was like--
All right. soldiers. Step down.
I'll take it from here.
Yes. ma'am. Sorry. ma'am.
Penny?
Ah. what the heck?
That make you mad?
No. why would you even--
- What are you doing?
- Deprogramming.
Okay. that
is weawy uncalled for.
What about this?
Was this called for?
Damn!
Excuse me. young lady.
but that is wildly--
Ow!
- Why aren't you being shocked?
- Shielding technology.
- Oh. great!
- Yeah. it's pretty tight.
When are you gonna
stop hitting us?
- When you get angry.
- Huh.
Are you angry?
No.
Yup!
I'm mad. I'm mad!
What about you?
Furious. and honestly.
a... a wittle turned on.
Yes. ma'am!
I don't understand.
Why did you rescue us?
Because I called them.
Thirty months ago.
What do you want from me?
I'm running a rebellion here.
Denise. you came back for me.
Not really.
I found your machine.
Show us how it can
get rid of the AI.
Oh. uh...
Yeah. I probably wasn't
clear about that.
It won't solve your AI problems.
Yeah. it'll just get us
out of your
happy-go-fascist universe.
Besides. we don't really know
how to use it.
We have some theowies.
So. wait. none of you know
how to defeat the AI overlord?
I don't. Bert?
- Nope.
- Kripke?
Not weawy.
Kill them!
- Wait! Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa!
- Uh...
Hold on. I-- I have an idea.
Fine. go ahead.
Now. it's a wong shot.
but it... it's worth a twy.
Hmm. okay.
Hmm. Mm.
Okay.
What is your idea?
Ah. if everyone would pwease
wook over there.
- He keeps doing that.
- Shoot him!
Oh. boy.
Oh. shit! They found us!
Okay. Shoot the drones!
Shoot the drones!
♪ Do unto others
As they've done to you ♪
♪ But what the hell
Is this world coming to? ♪
Come on. come on.
come on. come on. come on!
- Barry. wait!
- Sorry. fewas!
No. don't get shot. you idiot!
Oh. my God.
- Give me your hand.
- Why?
I don't wanna
have to find you again.
Oh. excuse me. I was about
to buy that Necronomicon.
Get over yourself.
You can't handle
this level of magic.
Uh... here.
Alchemy for Dummies.
That's more your speed.
I'll show you my speed.
Sempe faldinide un pera!
Oh. my God.
What happened? Where are we?
Make it stop!
- Please!
- Uh... Hang on.
Kyle?
I wasn't really gonna kill him.
Stop!
Fine.
Dnim reven.
You're such an asshole.
You want an asshole?
I'll show you an asshole.
Elohssa.
Kyle!
What is going on?
Wild guess?
We've landed in a universe
where magic is real.
Wait. this machine
actually worked?
- We're in another universe?
- It's. uh... It's crazy. right?
There's magic here?
What else explains
the. uh. asshole
on Trevor's head?
There's an asshole on my head?
Oh! Oh. great!
Well. the good news
is those joy buzzers are gone.
Oh. yeah. They are.
Oh. my God.
I have hemorrhoids.
I think we'll be safe here.
Burn the scientist!
Kripke. help me!
Hey. hey. uh.
is that weawy necessary?
Yes.
I twied.
Burn the scientist!
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Ah-ah ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Ah-ah ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Eh-eh ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Ah-ah ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Ah-ah ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Ah-ah ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ At least we know ♪
- ♪ Eh-eh ♪
- ♪ Where it's been ♪
- ♪ Ah-ah ♪
♪ Where it's been ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today